it is it's so great to be here i am a
comedian i wasn't always a comedian
actually was a stay-at-home dad
for a little while uh but then uh no
then we had kids
and uh
[Music]
had to get out of there and um it is an
honor to be here at dry bar comedy i was
a little nervous that the show wouldn't
go well because i requested
to have a bunch of creepy dolls behind
me the whole time and i thought they'd
forget
what in the world but it is it's so
great i love doing comedy i've been
doing this
uh for many years a lot of people want
to know what the worst uh part is and
honestly this is the best part it's
flying it's uh and the worst part is my
last name really is smiley
which is a great last name for comedian
is the worst last name
if you have to fly all the time because
every every tsa guy it even happened
this morning they look at my id and go
oh smiley how come you're not smiling
you got a last name smiley you ought to
smile all the time we're going to call
you mr frowny mr smiley let's see that
smile and all i can think of is man
i'm so close to your gun
but i have to smile because one time i
didn't one time i was overtired i've
been on this tour
uh i do a lot of christian uh advanced
churches so i was on this christian tour
called festival condios with uh
11 christian bands christian wrote
everything was christian even our
bathrooms we had first second and third
john
and
and they dropped me off uh in detroit
which is one of my favorite cities uh
i was there two weeks ago yeah so much
fun they took me around and
showed me how to draw a chalk outline of
a body and
with that that morning they dropped me
off it's like 4 a.m and i was like i
just wanted to get on the plane and um
uh in fact the whole tour started bad
because i
uh this isn't even part of my act but i
went to the library to get a book so i'm
a big reader and i got kicked out of the
library
um and the lady actually followed me out
she was like you can't yell in the
middle of the library i was like then
don't put pop-up books in the library
kind of bait and switch i was like oh
daniel in the lion's den
like so i yeah like
the whole flight it was hard actually i
almost got into it this morning i almost
didn't get because i got on the flight
and i was tired because i had to leave
uh at five this morning
and uh there's like i got on the plane
there's like a three foot male flight
attendant it was like you know fresh out
of the shire
and um no he was an angry hobbit
um because all i wanted to do was sleep
to get ready for the show and i walked
on and i grabbed a pillow out of first
class and he immediately grabbed it back
he was like
these are for first class passengers
you're in coach and you know i was going
to argue but
he'd already put the ring on it
disappeared and
it was so awkward because i was sitting
in bulkhead which is like the first of
like coaching stuff
and uh so he was making his and i don't
know if you guys fly a lot but he's
making his announcements and he's
staring right at me he's like
can everybody's attention please we
represent the
lollipop cat i know he didn't do that
i really wanted him to do that but no
i'm actually kind of glad he stared at
me though
because i've been flying for years i've
never listened to the announcements and
there's two announcements i can't
believe they haven't changed one
sorry i've never heard this before in
the event of a water crash landing
you can use your seat cushion as a
flotation device
okay guys think it through if i'm ever
in a really
really scary crash the seat cushion i
was just sitting on
[Music]
i don't want that thing anywhere near me
right
and the other one's even more dangerous
i thought when the oxygen mass falls
oxygen starts flowing it doesn't it says
to start the flow of oxygen
tug lightly on the tube well can we we
rethink that scenario who's going to be
going 10 000 miles an hour in a mountain
going ah
hehe
so flying's always annoying so this this
one this particular
moment uh when i got dropped off in
detroit this is why every single morning
i show my id and i just smile because
that morning i showed my id and this guy
wouldn't drop it
he just kept looking at and going smiley
you're not even smiling in the picture
is your last name really smiling why
aren't you smiling and he just kept
saying why are you smiling and i snapped
and this is why
i always get nervous when i fly because
that morning i was like you know what
i'll tell you why i'm not smiling it's 4
am
and ever since 9 11 i got to be at the
airport two hours early in order to get
grope before enjoying all my freedom
i also have to take my shoes off thanks
to the shoe bomber don't get me wrong
i'm glad he picked shoes and not a shirt
because i don't have the abs to pull
that off
i'm also going to be delayed because i'm
standing from the world's largest
redneck who has a belt buckle big enough
to serve tea
on but he can't figure out what's
setting off the metal detectors and that
doesn't even matter because we both know
i'm not going to fly today
because you're looking at my ticket you
see it says american airlines so we both
know
i'm going to be delayed i'm going to be
canceled i'm gonna get re-booked back
here tomorrow i get to try it all over
again but if it makes you feel any
[Laughter]
better
you